Hello!
Now, our guest this time is this idol!
This is Amehera Shinaida. Please give my regards to her.
Pleased to meet you.
Thank you very much.
It's outrageous.
Now, speaking of AmeFlash...
Last year, you got a lot of buzz on social networking sites like TikTok.
TikTok and other social networking sites last year.
I think it became a topic of conversation.
TikTok and other social networking sites.
What do you think of the response on social networking sites like TikTok?
What do you feel about the response to TikTok and social networking sites?
Well, I think everything has changed completely.
Our own concept and performance has not changed a bit.
Cool & Stylish" is still the same, but the content of our work
But the content of our work has changed.
There are fewer idol festivals and more artist-oriented festivals.
We have less idol festivals and more artist-oriented festivals,
I have been allowed to perform in the treatment group, and some of the members have also performed,
Also, my followers on Instagram and TikTok have increased a lot,
I was a little bit scared because of the increase,
Everything changed drastically. It was a bit scary, but I saw all the patterns and stuff.
Then, this project...
First of all, please show us the theme and make an announcement.
Yes, I will.
And so...
Well then!
Let's see what you want to do in the future!
Yay!
Yes, that's what I'm talking about.
From tomorrow onwards
I'll be announcing what Aira would like to do in the future
I'll be announcing your participation in the event.
Yes, please look forward to it!
Please look forward to it.
Nighttime and Idols
This program will be hosted by
Mr. Akki
Mr. Sadaaki
Mr. Sota
Mr. Fuuji
Mr. Tekohachi provided this program.
Thank you very much!
Thank you for watching!